# **SEBASTIAN KOZICKI**

open to remote work or relocation

8+ years

12+

500+

of design experience

programs &apps used visual projects







#### **CONTACT ME**

E-mail:

sebastian.kozicki1@gmail.com

PL mob.:

+48.601.50.32.63

FR mob.:

+33.631.98.08.66

#### **ABOUT ME IN A NUTSHELL**

UI/Web designer with the ability to empathize with people and create solutions that are simple, aesthetically pleasing and in line with client expectations. An experienced creative that has helped companies from over 8 industries meet clients' and employers' goals.

### **DESIGN TOOLS**

Figma Adobe

Adobe Xd CC PhotoShop CC

Illustrator CC

InDesign CC

VS Code WordPress

Miro / Notion / Trello ...and more

### AI SUPPORTING TOOLS

Relume

Uizard Autodesigner

Leonardo Ai

Chat GPT Bard / Open Ai / Perplexity

#### **DESIGN SKILLS**

typography / color layout composition wireframing / prototyping responsive web / app design HTML5 / CSS3

### SOFT SKILLS

fast learner looking globally communication goal orientation team player ...and more

### **LANGUAGE**

english: professional comunicative

polish: native

french: pre-beginner

## **SOME DESIGN ACTIVITIES**

### ux/ui hub

Vitamin K, 2024 my role: **UI designer** 

Cooperating with Vitamin K, providing ideas and design for the application and web, discussing UX writing, and helping with data filling out in Airtable.

### portfolio site

2023

my role: web designer / front-end developer

My portfolio website - I designed and coded the website myself using VS Code and the GitHub repository.

# responsive web application

toilet finder - cours project, 2023

my role: **UX/UI designer** 

Toilet Finder is a responsive web application based on geolocation. The project contained both UX and UI steps. I used design thinking, different ways of testing with users, SWOT, crazy 8', and Jakob Nielsen's error severity rating.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

### visual designer & creative consultant

05.2015 - present, 3C, Poland

I collaborate with diverse clients, assisting them in meeting their business needs while creating captivating and impactful visual experiences. Discuss, understand, conduct research, and develop projects considering the budget, use cases, and client's goals.

Clients receive valued market insight and high-quality materials following the agreed brief improves the clients' visibility and public appearance.

**I've been worked with cross-functional teams** from different countries (Poland, Eastern Europe, and Egypt) and **collaborated with developers** from the United States for private projects.

### team leader / printing technologist

11.2016 - 10.2018 & 11.2019-04.2021, bySolara, Poland

#### Coordinating a printing department of 3 people.

Managed the flow of materials along with the team, conducted desktop publishing projects review, acted as a connector between the sales and production departments and worked with the unique needs of clients and subcontractors.

Printed materials and ensured almost 100 percent quality and on-time delivery to customers.

### print & copy editing coordinator

06.2019 - 08.2019, Avon, Poland

## Deliver layout for Avon catalog every three weeks in ${\tt 5}$ languages.

Conducted desktop publishing and communicated with graphics to make recommendations and resolve issues.

Avon catalog was published on time every three weeks for 5 countries, ensuring product sales continued.

### **EDUCATION**